Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Ostraka, 11.75 linear feet in 10 small flat boxes
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 043, cuid32729 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 043)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 044, cuid32730 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 044)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 045, cuid32731 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 045)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 046, cuid32732 (Box 50, Item O.NYU inv 046)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 047, cuid32733 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 047)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 048, cuid32734 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 048)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 049, cuid32735 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 049)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 050, cuid32736 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 050)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 051, cuid32737 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 051)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 052, cuid32738 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 052)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 053, cuid32739 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 053)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 054, cuid32740 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 054)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 055, cuid32741 (Box 51, Item O.NYU inv 055)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 056, cuid32742 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 056)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 057, cuid32743 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 057)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 058, cuid32744 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 058)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 059, cuid32745 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 059)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 060, cuid32746 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 060)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 061, cuid32747 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 061)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 062, cuid32748 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 062)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 063, cuid32749 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 063)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 064, cuid32750 (Box 52, Item O.NYU inv 064)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 065, cuid32751 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 065)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 066, cuid32752 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 066)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 067, cuid32753 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 067)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 068, cuid32754 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 068)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 069, cuid32755 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 069)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 070, cuid32756 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 070)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 071, cuid32757 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 071)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 072, cuid32758 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 072)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 073, cuid32759 (Box 53, Item O.NYU inv 073)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 074, cuid32760 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 074)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 075, cuid32761 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 075)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 076, cuid32762 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 076)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 077, cuid32763 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 077)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 078, cuid32764 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 078)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 079, cuid32765 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 079)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 080, cuid32766 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 080)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 081, cuid32767 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 081)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 082, cuid32768 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 082)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 083, cuid32769 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 083)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 084, cuid32770 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 084)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 085, cuid32771 (Box 55, Item O.NYU inv 085)
  - Ostracon: O.NYU inv 086, cuid32772 (Box 54, Item O.NYU inv 086)
- Series III. Cuneiform Tablets, 1.25 linear feet in 1 small flat box
  - Two Cuneiform Tablets and Supporting Documentation (Including Translations), circa 2350 BC; cuid32773 (Box 56)
- Series IV. Mummy Wrappings, .25 linear feet in 1 oversized folder
  - Two Mummy Wrappings, cuid32775 (Box 45, Folder 2)